shopakira.com 2019-07-15

# Privacy & Security

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.shopakira.com (the “Site”)

## SECURITY

AKIRA uses security measures in order to protect from the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. All orders are transmitted over secure internet connections using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about IP address, web browser, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual products that you view, how you interact with the site, and what websites or search terms referred you to the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier.

“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

We use cookies to provide you with the best possible shopping experience.  
AKIRA collects information for the following purposes:  
The information is used to identify you while you shop, so that we can keep the items you have chosen in a "shopping cart".  
Performance data from your session will be used to improve the hardware and software used to provide this service.  
Data collected may be used to help us determine what additional features would be of benefit to you on this site.  
We may tailor the site experience specifically to you based on your current and past activities, which may include offering you products similar to those previously purchased or purchased by others.  
We may use information about you to tailor the site experience of another user that is similar to you, but without disclosing your identity or specific private information.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

## HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION? 

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you

Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

User Consent: We may use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, so that you can be provided with information about unrelated goods and services which we consider may be of interest to you.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

## SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

## BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING 

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by: Clear your browser cookies, and click “No” when prompted by our remarketing campaign permissions.

You can opt out of our email subscriptions by going to our email and clicking “Unsubscribe at the bottom footer of the email.”

## YOUR RIGHTS 

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

## DATA RETENTION 

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. We do not retain your payment information nor have access to it.

## CHANGES 

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

## CONTACT US 

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at customerservice@shopakira.com or by mail using the details provided below:

200 N. Fairfield Ave., Chicago, IL, 60612, United States
